<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Posts on The Weanie Wizards</title><link>https://recap.wizardswizardswizards.com/posts/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on The Weanie Wizards</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 10:32:42 -0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://recap.wizardswizardswizards.com/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Session 6 - They are Watched</title><link>https://recap.wizardswizardswizards.com/posts/session-6/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 10:32:42 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://recap.wizardswizardswizards.com/posts/session-6/</guid><description>&lt;h1 id="waterdeep-city-watch-incident-report">&lt;strong>Waterdeep City Watch Incident Report&lt;/strong>&lt;/h1>
&lt;p class="report">&lt;strong>Date of Incident:&lt;/strong> Hammer 15th, 1495 22:18pm&lt;br>
&lt;strong>Date of Submission:&lt;/strong> Hammer 16th, 1495 11:18 am&lt;br>
&lt;strong>Location:&lt;/strong> 152 Zastrow Street&lt;br>
&lt;strong>Incident Type:&lt;/strong> Peace Disturbance&lt;br>
&lt;strong>Responding Officer(s):&lt;/strong> Doug&lt;br>
&lt;strong>Reporting Officer(s):&lt;/strong> Captain Staget&lt;br>
&lt;strong>Case Number:&lt;/strong> A35122&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="responding-officers-actions" class="report">&lt;strong>Responding Officer&amp;rsquo;s Actions&lt;/strong>&lt;/h2>
&lt;p class="report">At approximately 18:34, while patrolling the Dock Ward, Officer Doug was approached by a Waterdavian citizen who alerted him to a potential altercation occurring in a nearby warehouse. Upon arriving at the scene, Officer Doug recognized the address as a warehouse previously listed as a location of interest. Officer Doug informed me of the disturbance. We responded swiftly, assembling an elite squad to conduct a raid on the warehouse.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Session 3-5ish - They Side Quest</title><link>https://recap.wizardswizardswizards.com/posts/session-3ish/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2024 20:23:04 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://recap.wizardswizardswizards.com/posts/session-3ish/</guid><description>&lt;p>I was utterly unprepared for the secrets hidden within Floon’s vault. As the safe door creaked open, we sat there, mouths agape at the sight before us. Inside, we found three potions of invisibility and 1,200 Dragons, meticulously arranged in twelve neat piles, along with an additional 200 Dragons haphazardly scattered about. But it was the letters that truly unsettled me. It appeared these Dragons had been obtained through morally questionable means, perhaps by witnessing, or participating in, some rather unsavory dealings.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Session 2 - They BNE</title><link>https://recap.wizardswizardswizards.com/posts/session-2/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 16:52:39 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://recap.wizardswizardswizards.com/posts/session-2/</guid><description>&lt;p>&amp;ldquo;I want to join your guild,&amp;rdquo; declared the diminutive gnome, launching into a heart-wrenching tale of familial treachery and homelessness. Ordinarily, I might have been vexed by such an unsolicited interruption, but the genuine joy radiating from this little fellow (or perhaps, a youthful man, you can never tell with the whimsical races) softened my resolve. Moved by his plight, I decided to welcome him into our fold with a Weanie Wizard patch of unparalleled distinction. After some deft magical work, we shifted our focus back to more pressing matters—namely, my own troubles.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Session 1 - They Fight</title><link>https://recap.wizardswizardswizards.com/posts/session-1/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2024 13:18:34 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://recap.wizardswizardswizards.com/posts/session-1/</guid><description>&lt;p>Even in a reputable establishment like the Yawning Portal, a bar fight is scarcely worth the attention when more pressing matters require your focus. My pressing matter, at that moment, lay at the bottom of my mug, where I hoped its contents might dull my concerns. The brawl seemed to involve Yagra Strongfist, a formidable half-orc who earned that surname, squaring off against a handful of humans. These misguided souls appeared to be taking her on one at a time—a bold, yet foolhardy approach, destined to end poorly for them.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Session 0 - They Meat</title><link>https://recap.wizardswizardswizards.com/posts/session-0/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 13:18:34 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://recap.wizardswizardswizards.com/posts/session-0/</guid><description>&lt;p>In the City of Splendors, some considered Waterdeep hot dogs the most splendid of the all its splendors. That&amp;rsquo;s why Steve Schelinski felt five feet tall when he heard the news: he had been picked by his firm to work for the Weenie Wizards. Finally, his break into hardcore accounting had arrived. No longer would he handle the books for small businesses or wealthy wizards. He was in the weenie business now, and people everywhere would respect him.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>